joomla2you.com 2017-08-12

# Privacy Policy

### General information

Privacy Policy of joomla2you is used in order to protect its customers privacy and security of information stored and shared with us through www.joomla2you.com. By registering and using our site you give consent automatically to use and disclose information if needed. Unless you agree with any terms below, you should not use products or services offered by joomla2you.

### Information collection and use

It is essential to collect your personal information in order to be able to make any purchase at joomla2you. It would be impossible to make purchase unless you share personal information with us. Additionally, your data has to be used while accessing technical support and it is required to make consent to this. Apart from that, in case of issuing invoices or other documents, the buyer is obliged to inform us about his/her detailed personal information such as name, address.

### Correcting/Updating Personal Information

You are free to update your information at any time directly through our site. If you want to update the email address in our site or change password,  log in at http://www.joomla2you.com and click on "Your Details" link.

### Protection of personal information

Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13th, for the Protection of Personal Data. Royal Decree 1720/2007, of December 21st, approving the implementing Regulation for Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13th, for the protection of personal data.

Information gathered and stored at joomla2you.com is fully protected. We do our best to secure data collected and do not disclose to any unauthorized person. All data is restricted to joomla2you employees and external service providers only and they are entitled to use your personal information, however, it is forbidden to misuse this data. If anyone uses classified data in the wrong way, we will take appropriate disciplinary action. 

However, we do not take responsibility for data used during PayPal payment as your personal information used there is not registered by our system and has to be protected by PayPal security system.

### Consent to disclose data

We need to have consent to disclose your personal information because it is impossible to make any purchase without it. If you do not agree to share this data with us, it will be barely possible to offer you any of our products.

At any time, you may inform us about not willing to share with us your personal information and disclosing it.
